The character repertoire of Aegyptus.otf is presented in the following files:

Gardiner.txt 
Hieroglyphs.txt
Meroitic.txt
Shading.txt
Tranliteration.txt

The actual glyphs can also be seen, if Aegyptus is set as the display font.

Bibliography

Nicolas Grimal, Jochen Hallof, Dirk van der Plas, “Hieroglyphica, Sign List”, 2nd edition, revised and enlarged by Jochen Hallof, Hans van den Berg, Gabriele Hallof, Publications Interuniversitaires de Recherches Egyptologiques Informatisées (PIREI I²), Utrecht – Paris, 2000

Baluk E. and Panov M., “The Hieroglyphica Project”, http://www.hieroglyphica.com, 2009

Allen, James P., “Middle Egyptian: an introduction to the language and culture of Hieroglyphs”, Cambridge: Cambridge University Press, 1999

Gardiner, Alan H.,
	“Catalogue of the Egyptian hieroglyphic printing type”, Oxford: Oxford University Press, 1928
	“Additions to the new hieroglyphic fount”, The Journal of Egyptian Archaeology 15, p. 95, London: Egypt Exploration Society, 1929
	“Additions to the new hieroglyphic fount”, The Journal of Egyptian Archaeology 17, pp. 245-247, London: Egypt Exploration Society, 1931
	“Supplement to the catalogue of the Egyptian hieroglyphic printing type”, Oxford: Oxford University Press, 1953
	“Egyptian grammar: being an introduction to the study of hieroglyphs”, 3rd edition, London: Oxford University Press, 1957

Möller, Georg, “Hieratische Paläographie”, 3 bands, Leipzig: J. C. Hinrichs’sche Buchhandlung, 1909, 1927, 1936, Osnabrück: Otto Zeller, 1965
